well I guess we can we can begin welcome
好吧，我想我们可以开始欢迎了
to to these talk streams in a while
在一段时间内转到这些谈话流
thank you for coming I hope you'll enjoy
谢谢您的光临，希望您会喜欢
your next 45 minutes in this room what I
您接下来的45分钟在这个房间里我
would like to talk to you about today is
想和你谈谈今天是
of course about the stream API
当然关于流API
introduced in Java 8 and especially to
在Java 8中引入，尤其是在
show you
给你看
advanced patterns with the stream API
流API的高级模式
basically based on the splitter ater
基本上基于分离器
API which is a an API from inside the
API，它是来自内部的API
stream API this will be mostly a live
流API，这将大部分是实时直播
coding session I hope you all liked live
编码会议，希望大家都喜欢直播
coding yeah do your previous lines but
编码是做您以前的内容，但是
at points plenty of bullet points many
在很多时候要点很多
many burritos I've got something for you
很多墨西哥卷饼，我为您准备了一些东西
for that showing that this work is
因为这表明这项工作是
mostly based on a work I've published on
主要是基于我发表的作品
huge on YouTube on github sorry a few
在github上的YouTube上巨大，对不起
months if not a little more than a year
几个月，如果不超过一年
ago an API called streams utils which is
之前一个称为stream utils的API
basically an API that extends what we
基本上是扩展我们
are going to show what I'm going to show
要显示我要显示的内容
you in a minute to come my name is Josie
一分钟后你来，我叫乔西
and live in a Paris area here are some
住在巴黎地区，这里有些
links with the some of my works you can
与我的一些作品链接，您可以
find on the on the Internet including a
在互联网上找到包括
youtube Botox my also proud member of
youtube Botox我也是
the Paris Java user group in case you
巴黎Java用户组，以防您
have questions just raise your hand
有问题只是举手
shout make some noise so that they can
喊叫声使他们可以
hear and see you and take a question do
听见和见到你，问一个问题
not hesitate to interrupt do not do not
毫不犹豫地打扰不要不要
wait for the for the end of the talk if
等待谈话结束，如果
you have questions and if you have
你有问题，如果你有
questions afterwards you can use this
之后的问题，您可以使用此
hashtag I'm always monitoring it so if
标签我一直在监视它，所以如果
you have it's a good way to interact
你有一个很好的互动方式
offline after after the conference and
会议结束后离线
that's it for the slides now I know that
现在就是幻灯片了，我知道
some of you probably like bullet points
你们中有些人可能喜欢要点
are I do not want to create any kind of
我不想创建任何种类的
frustration in the audience so I
观众的沮丧让我
gathered a bunch of bullet points here
在这里收集了一堆子弹点
for you guys
给你们
and that's it any Oracle OpenWorld only
就是任何Oracle OpenWorld
people in the room it shouldn't be
房间里的人不应该
saying that imagine the answer is true
说想像答案是正确的
what I'm looking at yes this I need to
我正在看的是的，这是我需要
switch this right and switch to here
切换此权限并切换到此处
this is an ID can you see it sit I will
这是一个ID，您能看到它吗，我会
favorite tool it is the phone big enough
最喜欢的工具是手机足够大
for everyone
为了每一个
yeah could it be bigger I can I do that
是的，它可以更大吗，我可以做到吗
print on to mode maybe where is it here
打印到模式也许在这里
presentation mode is it bigger
演示模式更大
not really yeah is it okay for everybody
真的不是吗，每个人都可以吗
okay fine so what do we have here we
好的，那我们在这里有什么
have a basic list of strings Java 8
有基本的字符串列表Java 8
style we we could have used the the
我们可以使用的样式
wonderful factory method from the list
列表中很棒的工厂方法
interface but this is this is still Java
接口，但这仍然是Java
8 code so it's not you all know that to
8个代码，所以不是所有人都知道
create a string on this we need to call
为此创建一个字符串，我们需要调用
the streamer method on it and from that
流媒体方法就可以了
we can just call for instance for each
我们可以为每个实例打电话
to print out the content of that stream
打印出该流的内容
of that stream
那个流
okay let us run this code great it does
好吧，让我们很好地运行此代码
what we expect it to do where did this
我们期望它在哪里做
stream method comes comes from it comes
流方法来自它来
from the default method from the
从默认方法
collection interface that in fact does
实际上的收集接口
two things create a splitter rater here
两件事在这里创建了一个分割器评分器
by calling another default method and
通过调用另一个默认方法
passing this Peter rater to a stream
将此彼得评分者传递给信息流
factory method of the stream support
流支持的工厂方法
class which can create stream and what
可以创建流的类以及什么
does this stream support class do it
这个流支持类做到了吗
does once again several things it
再次做几件事
creates an instance of this reference
创建此引用的实例
pipeline dot add class which is in fact
实际上是管道点添加类
the implementation and implementation of
的实施和实施
the stream interface itself and pass the
流接口本身并传递
splitter rater object we just created to
我们刚刚创建的分割器评分器对象
this implementation what what if
这个实现如果
if I'm showing you this code it's just
如果我向您显示此代码，
to show you that in fact the stream
向您展示实际上是流
object as an implementation as a runtime
对象作为运行时的实现
object is in fact created on two objects
对象实际上是在两个对象上创建的
well at least two objects first a
首先至少要有两个物体
reference pipeline object which is in
引用管道对象
fact where all the complex algorithms
所有复杂算法的事实
the map filter reduce collect stuff
地图过滤器减少收集东西
lives on and another object the splitter
生活在另一个对象分裂器上
rate object that is passed as a
对作为
parameter as a collaborator to this to
参数作为对此的协作者
this implementation and that is in fact
这个实现，实际上
meant to be to be overridden if I go
如果我去的话应该被覆盖
back to this split orator method I mean
回到我的分裂演说者方法
stream support hey sorry guys I'm in
流支持嘿对不起我
trouble with this presenter mode okay if
这个主持人模式的麻烦，如果
I if I go back to this to this splitter
我如果回到这个分离器
writer object here and see what it does
这里的作家对象，看看它做什么
it is indeed the default method from the
这确实是
from the collection framework but that
从收集框架，但那
is overridden in nearly all the classes
在几乎所有课程中都被覆盖
of the collection framework here's the
收集框架的是
the override of this split orator method
此拆分演说者方法的重写
from the ArrayList class for instance it
从ArrayList类，例如
returns an ASP literature that is that
返回的ASP文献是
is particular to this to this already
已经对此特有的
subject and in fact what does this
主题，实际上这是什么
pretreat object does it does the same
预处理对象的作用相同
kind of thing as the iterator does to
就像迭代器所做的那样
the collection implementations you know
您知道的集合实现
that we have a released and an iterator
我们有一个发布和一个迭代器
for our list the same for our set and an
对于我们的列表，对于我们的集合和
iterator for our set the stream API
设置流API的迭代器
works kind of the same we have the
作品有点一样，我们有
implementation where all the complexity
在所有复杂的地方执行
is and we don't want to look into that
是，我们不想调查
and an object that in fact hold the
和实际上持有
logic to access the data and this little
逻辑访问数据，这很少
rater object is is a little more complex
评价者对象稍微复杂一点
than the iterator object but it's still
比迭代器对象，但它仍然
fairly easy to implement yourself either
也很容易实现自己
to connect your streams up to particular
将您的流连接到特定
sources non-standard sources of data you
提供非标准数据来源
may have in your applications all to
可能在您的应用程序中
create streams of other streams once
一次创建其他流的流
we've seen that we can begin to play
我们已经看到我们可以开始比赛了
with
与
for instance a okay I'm going to take I
例如好吧，我要带我
need to take this code take the iterator
需要采取此代码采取迭代器
of the subject put this iterator in a
的主题将此迭代器放在
variable and just call create another
变量，然后调用创建另一个
stream by calling this stream support
通过调用此流支持
dot stream iterator and pass false the
点流迭代器并传递false
second parameter is a boolean now this
第二个参数是一个布尔值
boolean is true if you want this string
如果您想要此字符串，则布尔值为true
to be parallel and false if you do not
平行，如果不这样做则为假
want this dream to be part he I'm not
希望这个梦想成为他的一部分，我不是
going into this kind of thing think so
想到这种事情
I'm just going to keep this as a as a
我只是将其保留为
false or false value so this is a stream
假或假值，所以这是一个流
of string why isn't it happy with it
字符串为什么不满意
and from that I just want to catch that
从那我只想抓住那个
what problem do I have here I really
我真的在这里有什么问题
don't see yes thank you
看不到，谢谢
this is a splitter returning not the
这是一个分割器返回而不是
iterator and I'm going to call that
迭代器，我要称呼它
splitter Reiter Reiter all right
分配器Reiter Reiter好的
let us run this code and in fact it runs
让我们运行这段代码，实际上它可以运行
in the exact same way as the previous
与上一个完全相同
one okay so how can we create other
一个还可以，我们如何创建另一个
splitter raters starting from this
从此开始的分流评估者
little Reiter created on that stream let
在该流上创建的小Reiter让
us do that I'm going to first create a
我们要做的是，我将首先创建一个
very simple splitter ATAR that in fact
实际上非常简单的分离器ATAR
does nothing and it should be a good
什么也没做，应该很好
occasion just to visit the interface we
只是为了访问我们的界面
need to implement and see how the method
需要实现并查看方法
we need to implement work so I'm going
我们需要执行工作，所以我要去
to create a no operation of splitter
创建一个没有操作的分割器
ATAR of string no operation splitter
字符串无操作拆分器的ATAR
ater let us create this class real quick
Ater让我们快速快速地创建此类
I want to create it in that package
我想在那个包中创建它
great it implements speech orator of tea
伟大的它实现了茶演讲家
right what do we have here we have in
对，我们在这里拥有什么
fact a collection of methods to
事实是方法的集合
implement which are abstract method they
实现它们是抽象方法
are for them and for other methods that
是针对他们和其他方法的
are default methods that we do not need
是我们不需要的默认方法
to implement in a first step all right
第一步实施好
we will look into that more precisely
我们将更精确地调查
because there is a there is a trap in
因为那里有一个陷阱
that okay so this is our basic
好的，这是我们的基本
implementation I'm just going to do a
实现我只是要做一个
little further go a little further here
再往前走一点
because this knobs Peter Reiter is in
因为这个旋钮让彼得·雷特（Peter Reiter）
fact going to be created on the splitter
事实将在拆分器上创建
Reiter
瑞特
of the underlying stream so I'm going to
底层的流，所以我要
create this constructor great this is a
创建这个构造函数很棒，这是一个
splitter root of T indeed and I want to
确实是T的分离器根，我想
create that field and this idea is
创建那个领域，这个想法是
really great in hand I mean that right
真的很棒，我的意思是对的
so now I have this no operation splitter
所以现在我有了这个无操作分配器
a turd created on another splitter a
在另一个分割器上创建的草皮
turd itself created on an incoming
粪便本身在传入时创建
stream or on an upstream right what do I
流或上游的权利，我该怎么办
have to implement for that I have four
必须实施，我有四个
abstract method that I need to implement
我需要实现的抽象方法
of course if I do not do that it will
当然，如果我不这样做，它将
not work try advanced try split estimate
不起作用尝试高级尝试拆分估计
size and characteristics now you may
大小和特征，现在您可以
think that those methods have kind of
认为那些方法有
bizarre names on try split-- estimate
尝试拆分时使用奇怪的名称-估算
size and collection I have a size method
大小和集合我有一个大小方法
but I do not have an estimate size
但我没有估计的大小
method and this is in fact quite normal
方法，这实际上是很正常的
and it comes from the the way the
它来自于
streams work when you create a stream on
在以下位置创建流时，流会起作用
a source of object you ought not you do
你不应该做的对象的来源
not necessarily know how many object you
不一定知道你有多少个对象
are going to to process through that
将要处理
stream you don't do not know that when
流你不知道什么时候
you create a collection on an array list
您在数组列表上创建一个集合
for instance so set of object you know
例如，您知道的一组对象
exactly how many objects you have in
您到底有多少个物件
this ArrayList but it is not the case on
这个ArrayList，但事实并非如此
us of first stream if you create a
如果您创建一个第一流的我们
stream on on an ArrayList okay you know
在ArrayList上流式传输好吧，你知道
the number of objects you are going to
您将要对象的数量
consume but if you create a stream for
消费，但如果您为创建流
instance on a text file and there is the
文本文件上的实例，
method for that on bufferedreader class
该方法在bufferedreader类上
which is which is called lines
这就是所谓的线
this method reads on the stream on the
此方法在
lines of this text file even if you know
即使您知道此文本文件的行
that there are two megabytes of content
有两兆字节的内容
in this text file you do not know in
在此文本文件中，您不知道
advance how many lines they are in it
前进其中的行数
there may be one line or a million line
可能有一条线或一百万条线
or ten lines you need to analyze the
或十行您需要分析
text file for that so it's really a
文本文件，所以它实际上是一个
method estimate site that does that an
方法估算站点
estimation of the sides of the stream
估算河流两岸
in some cases this estimation may be
在某些情况下，这种估计可能是
accurate in some other cases it may be
在其他情况下可能是准确的
not accurate for the moment what I'm
目前我还不准确
going to do is just wire this method on
要做的就是将这种方法
the underlying split aerator so this
基础的分流曝气器
estimate size will just return the same
估计大小将返回相同
result as the estimate size of the
结果作为估计的大小
splitter rater I am creating on this tri
我在此三级上创建的分割器评分器
split method will be called if I want to
如果我想的话，将调用split方法
go parallel going parallel means I need
并行并行意味着我需要
to split my stream in two parts give the
将我的信息流分为两部分，
first part to a given Cove my CPU on the
第一部分到给定的Cove我的CPU
second part to another core my CPU
第二部分到另一个核心我的CPU
process stuff in parallel if I do not
如果我不并行处理东西
want to go parallel we fight I am sure I
想去平行我们战斗我确定我
will not go parallel I can return nil
不会并行我可以返回nil
with this try split method
用这个尝试拆分方法
characteristics for the moment I will
我现在的特征
not go into details in this method we'll
在此方法中我们不详细介绍
do that in a minute for the moment I
我暂时要一分钟
will just continue to return the
只会继续返回
characteristics of the underlying stream
底层流的特征
and now there is this trial runs method
现在有这个试运行方法
this is really where I need to write my
这真的是我需要写我的地方
code if I want to do stuff non trivial
代码，如果我想做一些琐碎的事情
stuff later let us state it like that
东西以后让我们这样说
this try advanced method can be seen as
这种尝试高级方法可以看作是
the equivalent of the next method of the
等价于下一个方法
of the iterator object but it works
迭代器对象，但可以工作
differently first it returns a boolean
不同的是，它首先返回一个布尔值
right and this boolean of force can be
对，这个布尔值可以是
true or false as many billions if it's
真假十亿
false it means that I do not have any
假意味着我没有任何
more object to produce with the splitter
分离器可生产更多物体
rater and if it returns true it means
评估者，如果返回true，则表示
that I should the implementation should
我应该执行
keep calling this right nonce method
继续调用此权利随机数方法
because more objects are coming okay and
因为更多的物体都可以了
now it takes also consumer as a
现在它也将消费者作为
parameter action
参数动作
we need to understand that this try
我们需要了解这种尝试
entrance method is going to be called by
入口方法将被调用
the reference pipeline object provided
提供的参考管道对象
the splitter rater is provided to that
分配器评级器被提供给
object so it's going to be called by the
对象，因此它将被调用
implementation and the implementation
实施和实施
will check if there are more objects to
将检查是否还有更多对象
be consumed and if they are we'll expect
被消耗，如果他们被我们期待
those objects to come at some point but
这些对象会在某个时候出现，但是
not necessarily at the moment at which
不一定在此刻
destroyed ones method is called we're
销毁的方法称为我们
going to to see examples of that later
以后再看例子
so this consumer is provided by this
所以这个消费者是由这个提供的
reference pipeline object and I should
引用管道对象，我应该
call the accept method of this consumer
调用此使用者的accept方法
with the object I want to consume okay
我要消耗的物体还可以
so somehow well I am on a splitter rater
所以我在分离器评分器上表现不错
created on an other splitter rater so if
在其他拆分器评分器上创建，因此如果
I want to know what objects are going to
我想知道什么东西要去
consumed by the stream I I mean I need
流II消耗掉意味着我需要
to call the underlying splitter rater so
调用基础拆分器评估器
in fact also called
其实也叫
this splitter rater dot try it once
这个分离器评分器点尝试一次
method and do the same that is provide a
方法，并做的是提供一个
consumer to this trade wanted to get the
这项交易的消费者想要获得
object produce by the underlying
底层产生的对象
splitter rater so let us provide the
分配器评分器，让我们提供
consumer this is a consumer doesn't do
消费者，这是消费者不做的
much this consumer will be called by the
这个消费者将被
underlying splitter rater the one I am
基本的拆分器评分器我是
built and created on and this object
在此对象上构建和创建
here will be will have to be passed to
这将必须传递给
the to the reference pipeline that is
到参考管道的
calling me so what I need to do is just
打电话给我，所以我需要做的就是
call action dot except of T right here
在这里呼叫除T以外的动作点
I'm not doing anything I'm just calling
我什么都没打电话
the underlying splitter ater hey do you
底层拆分器嘿，你呢
have object for me if so just call the
有东西给我，如果是这样，只需致电
consumer I'm giving you and if my
消费者我给你，如果我
consumer is called then I take the
消费者被称为然后我
object and call the other consumer given
反对并致电给定的其他消费者
to me with that object and this is the
对我来说就是那个
way an object is transmitted from a
从一个物体传输物体的方式
splitter rater to a stream by calling
通过调用将分割器评级器流化
this this consumer now this try and want
这个消费者现在这个想要
method method is going to return a brand
方法方法将要返回一个品牌
I'm going to call it as mall this
我将其称为购物中心
boolean will be true if they are more
如果它们更多，则布尔值将为真
object to consume
消费对象
and false if it's not the case so since
如果不是，则为false，因为
this literature is not doing anything I
这个文学我什么也没做
can just return this as more object just
可以将其作为更多对象返回
to to complete to complete the process
完成要完成的过程
and now if I check my calling code this
现在如果我检查我的呼叫代码
splitter Reiter I can just provide it
分离器Reiter我可以提供
here so this stream is now created on my
在这里，这个流现在在我的
operation splitter writer and I should
操作拆分器作者，我应该
not observe any kind of differences
没有观察到任何差异
since my no obliterator is not doing
因为我没有闭塞者没有做
anything so let us run this code and
任何事情，让我们运行这段代码，
indeed I have the exact same behavior as
实际上，我的行为与
previously minor op splitter it is not
以前较小的运算分配器不是
doing anything but then I can go one
做任何事情，但是我可以去
step further by creating for instance a
通过创建例如
splitter rater that is going to to block
将要阻塞的分配器评分器
some objects not transmitting all of
一些对象没有传输全部
them suppose we create a filter in
他们假设我们在
splitter rater
分配器评分器
of string now let us collect filtering
现在，让我们收集过滤条件
splitter rater I'm going to create it
分割器评分器，我要创建它
just as the previous one in this package
就像这个包中的上一个一样
I'm going to implement splitter rater of
我将实施
T and basically I will just have the
T，基本上我只会
same code as the no operation splitter
与无操作拆分器相同的代码
rater so I'm just going to copy paste
评价者，所以我要复制粘贴
all this yes this is a consumer alright
所有这些是的，这是一个消费者可以
I'm going to by the way also copy this
我要顺便也复制这个
the constructor this is the constructor
构造函数这是构造函数
of the filtering splitter rater and I'm
的过滤分离器评分器，我是
going also to pass a predicate as a
也将通过谓词作为
parameter predicate of T and I'm going
T的参数谓词，我要去
to call filter and just do that this
调用过滤器并执行此操作
filter
过滤
equals filter filter create the field
等于过滤器过滤器创建字段
just like that and now in my try
就像那样，现在在我的尝试中
advanced method what I want to do is say
我想做的高级方法是说
alright I see objects coming out from my
好吧，我看到有物体从我的身上冒出来
underlying splitter rater as long as I
底层分配器评分器，只要我
can see object I will continue to return
可以看到我将继续返回的对象
true because it means that I can produce
正确，因为这意味着我可以生产
more objects but I do not want to
更多的对象，但我不想
transmit the object that do not pass
传输不通过的对象
this filter here
这个过滤器在这里
so if filter the test of T is true then
所以如果过滤器T的检验为真，则
I transmit the object if it is false
如果它是假的，我将传输该对象
I do not transmit the object right let
我不传送物件吧
us see what it does
我们看看它做什么
so this filtering splitter rater is
所以这个过滤分离器评分器是
Cribs is created let's see an in on the
婴儿床已创建，让我们来看看
know operation splitter rater it needs a
知道操作分离器评估器，它需要一个
predicate of string
字符串谓词
let us select only the strings with
让我们只选择带有
length 3 and run the code okay so I need
长度3并运行代码，所以我需要
to create pass my stream here on this
在这里创建通过我的流
filter ring of course Peter ater
彼得·阿特（Peter ater）
and you see that this time only the
而且您看到这次只有
objects with 3 characters have been
具有3个字符的对象已
transmitted to the to do to the
传递给做
downstream we created on the filtering
我们在过滤上创建的下游
splitter rater so this you see that if I
分配器评分器，以便您看到如果我
show this example to you it just to show
给你看这个例子只是为了展示
you that it's not because I am returning
你不是因为我回来了
true that I need to transmit an object
是的，我需要传送一个物体
to the end to do to the downstream to
到下游去做
the downstream splitter ater right if I
如果我，下游分流器就对了
return true it just mean that I have
返回true，这意味着我有
more object to send but maybe not now
有更多对象要发送，但现在可能不发送
maybe maybe later and if you examine the
也许以后，如果您检查
stream API there are at least two
流API至少有两个
examples that works like that the first
像第一个那样的例子
one the most obvious one is the sorted
最明显的一种是排序
example to sort a set of objects you
排序一组对象的示例
need to see them all you cannot begin to
需要看到他们所有你不能开始
to produce object until you have seen
产生物体直到你看到
all the objects produced by this that's
所有由此产生的物体
dreama so this accept method will keep
梦想，所以这种接受方法将保持
answering true without producing
回答真实而不产生
anything
任何东西
and once the the up streamer is
一旦上行流是
completely consumed then the sorting
完全消耗掉然后分类
will occur and then the produce the the
将发生，然后产生
transmission of the object will be will
对象的传输将是
be done and the second example the
完成，第二个例子
distinct also these things were works
这些东西也很明显
with the mental index if an object
与心理指数，如果一个对象
resina
树脂
do we have already seen the subject if
我们是否已经看过该主题，如果
not then I transmit it if I did then
不，那么我会传输它
unblock it it's kind of adaptive
解锁它是一种自适应
filtering as you as in this case so in
在这种情况下像您一样进行过滤
fact this is a very classical way of
事实上，这是一种非常经典的方式
using this splitter Reiter Reiter Reiter
使用此分离器Reiter Reiter Reiter
stuff ASP literature can also be used to
东西ASP文献也可以用来
modify the object transmitted let us
修改传输的对象让我们
create a mapping splitter rater mapping
创建映射拆分器评分器映射
split a bit of string I'm going to keep
分割一点我要保留的字符串
it simple so I'm going to create the
很简单，所以我要创建
class once again in the splitter it's a
在拆分器中再次上课
package I'm going to yeah copy-paste all
包我要复制所有内容
this in fact all right not this one
实际上这不是这个
great so this is a mapping flip iterator
很棒，所以这是一个映射翻转迭代器
and in fact the second element is not
实际上，第二个要素不是
going to be a predicate but let's say a
将会是一个谓词，但假设
unary operator which I'm going to call a
一元运算符，我将其称为
mapper and this mapper will be a mapper
映射器，此映射器将是一个映射器
so I need to change this one again so
所以我需要再改变一次
now what I'm going to do is in fact oops
现在我要做的实际上是
is in fact remap this T object using
实际上是使用
this mapper this is my map using these
这个映射器，这是我使用这些地图
mappers I'm just going to call mapper
映射器，我要打电话给映射器
dot apply of T that is I am changing the
我正在更改的T的点适用
nature of the subject I am not changing
我没有改变主题的性质
the type but I could change the type as
类型，但我可以将类型更改为
well
好
and transmit this and transmit this
并发送此并发送此
transform object to to my to my to my
将对象转化为对我的转化为对我的转化
downstream so let us work that on
下游，让我们继续努力
example I'm going to take my filtering
例子我要过滤
splitter rater pass for instance strings
分割器评分器传递实例字符串
to uppercase like that this is my
像这样大写
mapping splitter rater and then on this
映射分配器评分器，然后在此
little rater
小评分者
I create a stream and see what it gives
我创建了一个流，看看它能给什么
and you see that both the filtering and
您会看到过滤和
the mapping have been applied that is
已经应用了映射
I've just changed my different splitter
我刚刚更换了不同的分配器
rater in the old chain okay but what I
老连锁店的评价员还可以，但是我
could do also so so here whatever I have
也可以这样做，所以无论我在这里
done I have blocked object I have
我已经挡住了我拥有的物体
transform object but I can also create
转换对象，但我也可以创建
more object in the downstream splitter
下游分配器中有更多物体
ater than I had in the upstream spitter
比我上游上游的要差
rater let us create a fourth wanna a
评分者让我们创建第四个想要的
repeating splitter rater
重复分配器评分器
of stream repeating splitter return let
流重复拆分器返回让
us let us create this class
我们让我们创建这个类
here going to copy paste this code to
这里将复制此代码粘贴到
make things quicker I implement splitter
使事情更快我实现了拆分器
rater this is a repeating a splitter
评价者，这是​​一个重复的分割器
rater and I can for instance pass an
评分者，例如，我可以通过
integer as a parameter this repeat oops
整数作为此重复操作的参数
equals repeat yeah create the field
等于重复是的，请创建该字段
thank you and then each time I get an
谢谢，然后每次我得到一个
object what I want to do is repeat that
反对我想做的是重复
object the number of time I haven't
反对我没有的时间
passed it so if repeat is equal to three
通过它，所以如果重复等于三
for instance I want to repeat the object
例如我想重复对象
incoming object three times so I can do
传入对象三遍，所以我可以做
that
那
I guess like that in stream dot range
我猜在流点范围内
from zero to n so you repeat and then
从零到n，所以您重复然后
for each index actually accept yes that
对于每个索引实际上接受
should do the trick
应该做到的
right if I go back to this stuff yes I
好吧，如果我回到这些东西，是的，我
need to instantiate it new repeating
需要实例化它新的重复
splitter later on the filtering splitter
稍后在过滤分离器上分离
return by a factor of two create the
以两倍的回报创建
stream on it run the code and you see
流上运行代码，您会看到
this time whoops
这次喔
what did I'm oh yes I didn't take the
我是怎么了哦，是的，我没有
mapping splitter it let us take the
映射拆分器
mapping splitter later okay so here you
映射分配器以后可以，所以在这里
see that every element has been repeated
看到每个元素都被重复
twice so you really ask a question
两次，所以你真的问一个问题
yeah
是的
you mean in try advance
你的意思是提前尝试
[Music]
[音乐]
yeah that's okay that's okay this is
是的，这没关系，这是
what it's not doctor deprecated that
不是医生不赞成的
does not agree with that
对此表示不同意
why not
为什么不
so yeah you're just allowed to call the
所以是的，你只可以打电话给
consumer once I assure that so this is a
消费者一旦我保证，这是一个
bag I discuss about that more I really
我真的要讨论更多
wonder how you're sorted method can work
想知道您如何对方法进行排序
if you do not allow this kind of thing
如果你不允许这种事情
so you're not allowed to do that hmm if
因此，如果您不允许这样做，
you change the behavior in 10 that is in
您更改了10中的行为
21 10 10.3 all right well it works right
21 10 10.3很好，它正常工作
it's pretty well
很好
yes we're not doing power there clearly
是的，我们没有在那里清楚地供电
clearly there is another point I would
显然我还有一点
like to raise it at this split orator
喜欢在这个分裂的演说家那里提出来
estimate size here because obviously I'm
在这里估算尺寸，因为显然我是
multiplying the the size of this
乘以这个的大小
predator by the repeat factor this is
捕食者的重复因子是
alone and the estimate size might be
一个人，估计大小可能是
long that max value in some cases so if
在某些情况下将最大值设置为最大值
I just return repeat time this splitter
我只是返回这个分割器的重复时间
ATAR
阿塔
repeat here time this splitter Reiter
在此重复此拆分器Reiter的时间
estimate size here am I going to trouble
估计这里的大小我会麻烦吗
because this long might become negative
因为这很久可能会变成负面
if this estimate size is itself from my
如果这个估算值本身来自我
long dot max value so I'm not going to
长点最大值，所以我不会
write this I'm going to keep it this is
写这个，我要保留它，这是
just an estimation anyway so I'm just
无论如何只是一个估计，所以我只是
going to keep it like that I just told
我要告诉我
you a few minutes ago that it was that
几分钟前你就是
sorry that implementing those four
对不起，实施这四个
methods was was enough to implement a
方法足以实施
splitter rater in fact it's not exactly
分配器评分器实际上并不完全
the case suppose this splitter rater
该案例假设此分配器评分器
here becomes sorted right could do that
这里变成正确的可以做到这一点
run this code and here I will get an it
运行此代码，在这里我会得到它
illegal state exception coming from the
来自的非法国家例外
gate comparator method of the splitter
分离器的门比较器方法
Reiter interface and if I check that
Reiter界面以及是否检查
indeed the default method of the
确实是
splitter Reiter interface throws this
splitter Reiter接口抛出此错误
illegal state exception now this gate
非法国家例外现在这扇门
comparative method is called by the
比较方法由
reference pipeline object only in the
引用管道对象仅在
case of a sorted stream so I have I can
排序流的情况下，我可以
do two things here either I say alright
我可以在这里做两件事
this stream is not sorted whether I
无论我是否对此流进行排序
provide a comparator from that stream
提供该流的比较器
note that here I sorted my stream
请注意，在这里我对我的信息流进行了排序
explicitly but suppose I have a method
明确地但我想有一个方法
that takes a collection any correction
需要进行任何更正的集合
and I call stream on that correction
我把这个修正称为流
that correction could also be for
更正也可能是为了
instance at reset let us do that
重置实例让我们做到这一点
quick reset of string created on this
快速重置在此创建的字符串
sorry on this released string them pass
对不起，这个释放的字符串他们通过
this reset here and now since this reset
此重置，这里和现在，因为此重置
is a sorted set in fact the stream
实际上是一个有序集
produced is automatically sorted itself
产生的内容会自动分类
and I have the exact same bird Iligan
我有完全一样的鸟伊利甘
state exception right so here what can I
声明异常权，在这里我该怎么办
do I'm going to my know up splitter ater
我要去了解我的分流器吗
here and if the underlying stream of
在这里，如果基础流
this node splitter ater is itself sorted
此节点拆分器本身已排序
it's quite normal to have assorted beta
有各种各样的beta是很正常的
beta so what I need to do is provide a
测试版，所以我需要提供一个
comparator let me override this gate
比较器让我覆盖此门
comparator method by providing this
通过提供此比较器方法
pizza rater
披萨评分器
get comparator method object here and I
在这里获取比较器方法对象
will have to do the same in fact for all
实际上，所有人都必须做同样的事情
my comparator splitter rater let me copy
我的比较器分配器评分器让我复制
paste this splitter rater sorry the
粘贴此分离器评分器，对不起
filtering splitter rater
过滤分离器评分器
quite obviously will not change the
很显然不会改变
salted nature of the streamer so I can
流光的盐渍性质，所以我可以
do the same provide also a comparator
做同样提供一个比较器
here the mapping splitter rater since it
这里是映射拆分器评估程序，因为它
can change the nature of the object
可以改变物体的性质
probably change a string into an integer
可能将字符串更改为整数
or person into the name of that person
或某人的名字
it will most probably change the salted
它很可能会改变盐味
nature of that stream so this time watch
该流的性质，所以这次要注意
what I should save for this potato is
我要为这个土豆保存的是
that the produced stream is not sorted
产生的流没有排序
in any case and to do that I need to
无论如何，要做到这一点，我需要
touch these characteristics method here
在这里触摸这些特征方法
in fact this characteristic subject is a
实际上，这个特色学科是
word field of bits and each bit each bit
位的字字段，每个位每个位
of this word has a meaning there is one
这个词的意思是有一个
that is the sorted bit so if I want to
那是排序的位，所以如果我想
say that this characteristics are not
说这个特性不是
sorted anymore I need to
排序了，我需要
at the logical end with it to set the
在逻辑上设置它
sorted bit to zero and this is the right
排序为零，这是正确的
way of doing it the repeating speed
重复速度的方法
generator would probably not change the
发电机可能不会改变
thus altered the nature of this of this
因此改变了这个的性质
trimmer and I think that's it so if I
微调，我想就是这样
run this code again now I have fixed all
现在我已经修复了所有问题，再次运行此代码
my streams either it's not so non sorted
我的信息流不是那么没有排序
either it's sorted and it can provide
它可以被排序并且可以提供
the comparator so now I do not have the
比较器，所以现在我没有
back anymore but I still have another
回来了，但我还有另一个
bug in this code beside the fact that
除了以下事实外，此代码中的错误
I'm calling accept twice I really think
我真的想过两次打电话接受
I can which is which is the following
我可以是以下哪个
when I'm when I'm closing a stream in
当我关闭流中的时候
fact let me what can I do here let me
其实让我在这里我能做什么让我
just comment this code for the moment
暂时评论一下这段代码
like that we'll come back to it later
这样我们以后会再讲
and just produce the stream here and I'm
然后在这里产生流，我就是
going to to just to print out the result
只是为了打印出结果
of that stream system that I would
我想要的那个流系统
printer so if I run this code it will
打印机，所以如果我运行此代码，它将
print out the result we all know that
打印结果，我们都知道
but what I can do is set a callback on
但我能做的是在
the close method on a close call of that
close调用时的close方法
stream sorry let me put this in variable
抱歉，让我将此变量放入变量中
right call stream on closer provide a
正确的呼叫流在更近处提供
runnable for instance system out closing
可运行，例如系统关闭
okay and closer explicitly and call the
好的，更明确地联系，然后致电
close method on that stream if I run
如果我运行，则在该流上关闭方法
this code then I will have all the
这段代码，我将拥有所有
content of the streamer displayed here
此处显示的流媒体内容
and the closing method the closing
和关闭方法关闭
message appearing since this callback
此回调之后出现的消息
has been called here now if I keep this
如果我保留这个，现在被叫到这里了
callback here so now
现在在这里回调
we get rid of this code and and come on
我们摆脱了这段代码，然后继续
that all right so here I'm going to fall
没事，所以我要跌倒了
back to this stream here
回到这里
Cora stream to there under stream to
科拉流到流下
there if I close my stream to here I set
如果我将流关闭到此处，我会在那里
up a callback did I set up a callback
设置了回调吗？
yes the set up the callback is set up
是的，设置回调
here this tree set is not used anymore
这里不再使用这个树集
and I'm just creating this predator on
我只是在创建这个掠食者
this stream here and calling the close
此流在这里，并呼吁关闭
method of the of the stream I have built
我建立的流的方法
on this one but if I if I run this code
关于这一点，但如果我运行这段代码
in fact this code the callback of the
实际上这段代码的回调
first stream is not cold anymore and it
第一流不再冷，它
should be since it's a callback and all
应该是因为这是一个回调，所有
the streams should should call that
流应该调用
close method themselves so every time I
自己关闭方法，所以每次我
am creating a stream like that on a
正在创建一个像这样的流
splitter ater what I should be doing
我应该怎么做
really is a stream to call the on close
真的是一个叫关闭的流
and call the streamer close method of
并调用流的close方法
the other stream my splitter ater have
我的拆分器另一条流
been created on this splitter Reiter is
在此拆分器上创建的Reiter是
created on the stream then all the other
在流上创建，然后所有其他
splitter raters are created on this one
分配器评分者在此创建
right so this is the stream that I need
对，所以这是我需要的信息流
to to to the callback has been defined
到回调已定义
on this dreamer and closing that stream
在这个梦想家并关闭那条小溪
created on the other one should also
在另一个上创建的还应该
call the callback of this one so now if
调用这个的回调，所以现在如果
I run my code I have the closing method
我运行我的代码我有关闭方法
that is properly called so in fact when
正确地称呼它，事实上，当
implementing a splitter ater there is
实施分离机
the technical part implementing the for
实施的技术部分
abstract method that's okay we saw that
好的抽象方法，我们看到了
but I also need to be sure that this on
但我还需要确保
close method should the on close method
close方法应为on close方法
well the closing callback is properly
那么关闭回调是正确的
called when closing the new stream I'm
在关闭新流时调用
creating on the splitter ater and I also
在分离机上创建，我也
need to make sure that
需要确保
I am probably properly and linked salted
我可能是正确的并链接咸
the salted stream that may raise
可能上升的咸流
exception if if I do not handle them
如果我不处理它们，则为例外
properly so those are the three the two
正确的，所以这是三个两个
main traps in in handling those streams
处理这些流的主要陷阱
in fact questions yeah yes sometimes you
其实是的，是的，有时候你
can open streams on our resources which
可以在我们的资源上打开流
is the case for the bufferedreader for
是针对的bufferedreader的情况
instance so closing calling the close
实例，所以关闭调用关闭
method on the stream should be closing
流上的方法应关闭
also your i/o through which resource
还有你的I / O通过哪些资源
that you that you've been using in fact
实际上，您一直在使用的您
the stream extends auto crucible so you
流扩展了自动坩埚，因此您
can use a stream in in a try with
可以尝试使用流
resource api when you're just calling
只需调用资源API
streams on ArrayList and you don't call
流在ArrayList上，您不调用
the close method yourself it will not be
您自己的关闭方法不会
very very harmful but if you're using io
非常非常有害，但是如果您使用io
resources then you should definitely do
资源，那么你绝对应该做
that other questions yeah
还有其他问题
does the splitter return needs to be
分离器返回是否需要
thread-safe it really depends on whether
线程安全，这实际上取决于是否
you are using it in parallel or not if
您是否并行使用它，如果
you're using it in parallel the API will
您正在并行使用它，API将
call this tri split method and you
叫这个三分裂的方法，你
should be returning another splitter
应该返回另一个拆分器
later on a portion of that stream so in
稍后在该流的一部分中
itself it depends if you have a shared
本身取决于您是否共享
state in it or not but Denis in itself
是否声明但丹尼斯本身
all the other methods that do not need
所有其他不需要的方法
to be synchronized and should not be
要同步，不应
synchronized by default all right I
默认情况下同步我
think that we are kind of running out of
认为我们有点用光了
time so I just added a few slides as a
时间，所以我只是添加了几张幻灯片作为
reference the different meaning of the
引用不同的含义
different bits of this characteristics
这种特性的不同之处
word we just saw during the during the
我们刚刚在
the the live coding part of the stuff
这些东西的实时编码部分
they are basically self-explanatory and
他们基本上是不言而喻的，
maybe sighs the mean that you are
也许叹息着你的意思
opening a splitter later on a structure
稍后在结构上打开拆分器
that knows the amount of element it will
知道元素的数量
is going to create think of an array
将要创建一个数组
list for instance or are set and sub
列出实例或设置和子
size them which is the other one that is
调整大小，这是另一个
maybe non-trivial means that if you
也许不平凡意味着，如果你
split the source of your of your of your
分割您的来源
streamer if you go parallel then the
流光如果你去平行然后
splitting will also produce elements
分裂也会产生元素
while sub streams that are sized if you
而子流的大小，如果您
split an ArrayList in two you can you
可以将ArrayList分成两部分
can count the number of elements in each
可以计算每个元素的数量
part of the array list if you split an
如果拆分一个数组列表的一部分
asset into by by cutting the underlying
通过削减基础资产
array you have in an asset or in the
资产或资产中的数组
Nash map into you cannot foresee how
纳什映射到您无法预见
many elements they are in the right path
他们在正确的道路上有很多要素
and in the left part of this array so
在这个数组的左边
the sides for our set for instance is
例如我们布景的边是
false whereas it's true for erased and I
错误，而擦除则为真，我
also give you a hint at the stream duty
还给您提示河流责任
API that you can find on on github your
您可以在github上找到的API
there are many more sophisticated
还有很多更复杂的
operation than the mapping filtering no
操作比映射过滤没有
op which was really easy one available
op，这真的很容易
like grouping rolling zipping they are
就像分组滚动拉链一样
they are I think 20 or 19 operates
他们是20或19
different operate on it and you have
不同的操作，你有
also an an operator which does a
也是一个
collection on a shifting window which is
在移动窗口上收集
extremely useful when you have a huge
当您拥有大量商品时非常有用
stream of elements and you want to to
元素流，您想
compute an average for instance and on
计算平均值，例如
the shifting window in average it's just
平均而言，移动窗口只是
a special case of a fur collection so
皮草收藏的特例
you can you can do that you can also the
你可以做到，你也可以
results I also put an efficient
结果我也把高效
algorithm to extract the N maxes of a
提取a的N个最大值的算法
given stream which is a useful in many
给定的流在许多情况下都是有用的
cases so this is the link to the stream
案例，所以这是到流的链接
API conclusion yes if you want to
API结论是，如果您想
connect your stream algorithm and on
连接您的流算法并继续
your own sources of data well you can do
您自己可以做的数据源
that by your fiddling with the splitter
通过摆弄分离器
rate or API it's not that easy it's a
费率或API并非易事，
little tricky but it's very powerful and
有点棘手，但功能非常强大，
it will it will really allow it really
它将真的允许它真的
allows you to leverage all the powerful
使您可以利用所有强大的功能
algorithm that are in the behind the
后面的算法
stream API which is which is really
流API，这实际上是
great and I also provided the link with
很好，我还提供了链接
my github account and with that I think
我的github帐户，我认为
we don't thank you for your attention I
我们不感谢您的关注我
don't know we still have a few minutes
不知道我们还有几分钟
for questions if you have if you have
询问是否有
any yeah please
是的，请
I don't know if any threshold really it
我不知道是否真的有任何门槛
really depends on what you what you need
确实取决于您的需求
to do so then I I never I never came
这样我就永远不会来
across any kind of problem with this
遇到任何与此有关的问题
with this stuff and I really had to to
这些东西，我真的不得不
manage large amount of data with not big
用不大的数量管理大量数据
data side terabytes of data but in
数据端TB级的数据，但在
memory large sets of data and I could do
存储大量数据，我可以做
that very easily going parallel is
那很容易并行
always a more complexity and I would not
总是更加复杂，我不会
recommend going parallel if you not
建议您并行使用
really sure that what you're doing
真的确定你在做什么
stay stay in a non parallel world as
留在一个非平行世界
long as you can because going parallel
只要你可以，因为平行
might in fact decrease your performance
实际上可能会降低您的表现
instead of of increasing them be
而不是增加他们
extremely careful with that any other
与其他任何东西都非常小心
questions
问题
okay so thank you I'll make this slide
好的，谢谢，我将制作这张幻灯片
on a variable on my SlideShare account
在我的SlideShare帐户上的变量上
very soon so you can check that and I
很快，您可以检查一下，我
will tweet about
将发布有关
[Applause]
[掌声]